[
  {
    "question": "What is the fourth digit of pi?",
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do employers need to have guard railings?",
    "answer": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "question": "What electrical component opposes the flow of current in a DC circuit?",
    "answer": "Resistor"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why did Grayton get angry?",
    "answer": "His code didn't work"
  },
  {
    "question": "Daniel",
    "answer": "Sanbeg"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why did David not do his work?",
    "answer": "To read the lesson"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a common repeater frequency offset in the 2 meter band?",
    "answer": "600 kHz"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the approximate velocity of a radio wave in free space?",
    "answer": "300,000,000 m/s"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the meaning of life",
    "answer": "Burrito"
  },
  {
    "question": "Taco or Burrito",
    "answer": "Taco"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is Taco the meaning of life?",
    "answer": "No"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is a orange?",
    "answer": "Purple"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why is Thor so fat in Avengers Endgame?",
    "answer": "He got sad"
  },
  {
    "question": ".",
    "answer": "Boy"
  },
  {
    "question": "Once upon a time there was a",
    "answer": "Banana"
  },
  {
    "question": "Enter a question:",
    "answer": "Enter a answer:"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why is Grayton failing?",
    "answer": "Dumb"
  },
  {
    "question": "Enter",
    "answer": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the guy that does the enderman riding hog?",
    "answer": "Hogrider"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who's the big guy that shoots a bow in hit game Clash of Clans 2091?",
    "answer": "Archer"
  },
  {
    "question": "Bob the",
    "answer": "Builder"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sponge",
    "answer": "Bobb"
  }
]